
export const Questions = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: 'Which of the following is Chemical formula of Water?',
        options: ['H20', 'H202', 'HCL', 'H2SO4'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Force in circular Motion is __',
        options: ['Tangent', 'Torque', 'Momentum', 'All Above'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'DX12 is ___',
        options: ['Language', 'Hardware', 'API', 'None'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Unit of Power is',
        options: ['Watt', 'Kilo Joules', 'Hertz', 'Meter per second'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Can you download RAM Online?',
        options: ['Yes', 'No', 'Both', 'None of Above'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'Which of the following is also called translator?',
        options: ['Data representation', 'MS-DOS', 'Operating System', 'Language Processor'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'The largest Ambulance Service in the World?',
        options: ['Edhi Foundation', 'Searne ptd.', 'Bajaj foundation', 'Faulkaners International'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Who won Cricket WorldCup 1999?',
        options: ['Bangladesh', 'Canada', 'Australia', 'New-Zealand'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What does the command prompt uses?',
        options: ['CLI (Command Line Interface)', 'GUI (Graphical User Interface)', 'Text User Interface TUI', 'None of the above'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What is our National Language?',
        options: ['English', 'Pashtoo', 'Urdu', 'Hindi'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'Which Company manufactures GPU?',
        options: ['Nvidia', 'Honda', 'Lisp', 'All of the above'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'What is the full of form ALU?',
        options: ['Analyst Logic Unit', 'Algebraic Logic Unit', 'Arithmetic Logic Unit', 'None of the above'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: 'Which out of the following is the file extension of for all Word documents?',
        options: ['Txt', 'Doc', 'PDF', 'Word'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: 'What does PPI stand for?',
        options: ['Pixel Per Square Inch', 'Security System', 'Packet Property Integration', 'None of the above'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: 'The speed of a CPU is measured in what?',
        options: ['Hertz (Hz)', 'Velocity', 'MegaPixel', 'Acceleration'],
        answer: 0
    },
]